http://www.deccanchronicle.com/privacy-policy

Prayers
IPL 2020NationCrimeCurrent AffairsPoliticsIn Other NewsWorldAustralia and New ZealandNeighboursAsiaAfricaAmericaEuropeMiddle EastSouthTelanganaAndhra PradeshTamil NaduKarnatakaKeralaEntertainmentTheatreMusicBollywoodKollywoodSandalwoodTollywoodTelevisionMovie ReviewsMollywoodHollywoodSportsBadmintonCricketFootballTennisIn Other NewsTechnologyGadgetsIn Other NewsMobiles and TabsLifestyleViral and TrendingHealth and WellbeingSex and RelationshipFashion and BeautyFood and RecipesTravelBooks and ArtEnvironmentCulture and SocietyGalleryBusinessAutosCompaniesEconomyIn Other NewsMarketOpinionSunday ChronicleDecafDiscourse360 DegreeHyderabad ChronicleChennai ChronicleBengaluru ChronicleKerala ChronicleScienceEditors' PicksJust InVideosAstroguidePlay Games
e-Paper |
Sunday Chronicle
Auto Refresh
| Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process
Friday, Dec 11, 2020 | Last Update : 11:15 AM IST
IPL 2020NationWorldSouthEntertainmentSportsTechnologyLifestyleGalleryBusiness
More...
OpinionSunday ChronicleDecafDiscourse360 DegreeHyderabad ChronicleChennai ChronicleBengaluru ChronicleKerala ChronicleScienceEditors' PicksJust InVideosAstroguidePlay Games
Privacy PolicyDeccanchronicle.com is the digital face of Deccan Chronicle Holdings Limited ('DCHL' or 'Company') that publishes the largest circulated English newspaper in South India -- the Deccan Chronicle.
We bring readers the most comprehensive bouquet of news and analysis every minute. Our fearless and unbiased journalism over the last 76 years has won the Deccan Chronicle a mature and dedicated readership from all over the world. And, it is growing.
Deccanchronicle.com wishes to inform, engage and entertain readers with a wide variety of content that is both timely and accurate. Deccanchronicle.com continues to build on its strong base of readers from the south of India while breaking new ground with readers in India and the world.
The Deccan Chronicle is proud of its practices and committed to maintaining robust privacy protection for its users. This statement governs your use of the site, its content and other services (collectively called the Service).
Our Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand how we collect, use and you provide us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our services.
For purposes of this agreement, Service refers to the Company’s service which can be accessed via our website at deccanchronicle.com ('Site') or through our iOS and android mobile and tablet applications in which users engage with our site.
The terms 'we', 'us', and 'our' refer to the Company. 'You' or 'your' refers to you, as a user of Service. By accepting our Privacy Policy, you consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.
REGISTRATION
Registration for a Service may require you to use a username and a password. You may supply us with certain personal information, including a unique email address. The Company may verify your email address before your account can be used.
You may use a third party account with your registration. By associating your accounts, you are giving these third parties permission to send us certain information from your profile. The information sent to us by them depends on your privacy settings with those third parties.
You agree to provide truthful and complete information when you register for the Service and to keep that information updated. You are personally responsible for any use of the Service.
You can cancel your registration with the Company at any time, as well as sever the third party accounts.
INFORMATION WE COLLECT
We collect 'Non-Personal Information' and 'Personal Information'. Non-Personal Information includes information that cannot be used to personally identify you, such as anonymous usage data, general demographic information we may collect, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, preferences you submit and preferences that are generated based on the data you submit and number of clicks. Personal Information includes only your email, which you submit to us through the registration process at the Site.
a. Information collected via Technology
To activate the Service you do not need to submit any Personal Information other than your email address. To use the Service thereafter, you do not need to submit further Personal Information. However, in an effort to improve the quality of the Service, we track information provided to us by your browser or by our software application when you view or use the Service, such as the website you came from (known as the 'referring URL'), the type of browser you use, the device from which you connected to the Service, the time and date of access, and other information that does not personally identify you. We track this information using cookies, or small text files which include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to a user’s browser from our servers and are stored on the user’s computer hard drive. Sending a cookie to a user’s browser enables us to collect Non-Personal information about that user and keep a record of the user’s preferences when utilizing our services, both on an individual and aggregate basis.
The Company may use both persistent and session cookies; persistent cookies remain on your computer after you close your session and until you delete them, while session cookies expire when you close your browser.
b. Information you provide us by registering for an account
In addition to the information provided automatically by your browser when you visit the Site, to become a subscriber to the Service you will need to create a personal profile. You can create a profile by registering with the Service and entering your email address, and creating a user name and a password. By registering, you are authorizing us to collect, store and use your email address in accordance with this.
HOW WE USE AND SHARE INFORMATION
Personal Information:
Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not sell, trade, rent or otherwise share for marketing purposes your Personal Information with third parties without your consent. We do share Personal Information with vendors who are performing services for the Company, such as the servers for our email communications who are provided access to user’s email address for purposes of sending emails from us. Those vendors use your Personal Information only at our direction and in accordance with our privacy policy.
In general, the Personal Information you provide to us is used to help us communicate with you. For example, we use Personal Information to contact users in response to questions, solicit feedback from users, provide technical support, and inform users about promotional offers.
Non-Personal Information:
In general, we use Non-Personal Information to help us improve the Service and customize the user experience. We also aggregate Non-Personal Information in order to track trends and analyse use patterns on the Site. This Privacy Policy does not limit in any way our use or disclosure of Non-Personal Information and we reserve the right to use and disclose such Non-Personal Information to our partners, advertisers and other third parties at our discretion.
In the event we undergo a business transaction such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your Personal Information may be among the assets transferred. You acknowledge and consent that such transfers may occur and are permitted by this Privacy Policy, and that any acquirer of our assets may continue to process your Personal Information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. If our information practices change at any time in the future, we will post the policy changes to the Site so that you may opt out of the new information practices. We suggest that you check the Site periodically if you are concerned about how your information is used.
HOW WE PROTECT INFORMATION
We implement security measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access. Your account is protected by your account password and we urge you to take steps to keep your personal information safe by not disclosing your password and by logging out of your account after each use. We further protect your information from potential security breaches by implementing certain technological security measures including encryption, firewalls and secure socket layer technology. However, these measures do not guarantee that your information will not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of such firewalls and secure server software. By using our Service, you acknowledge that you understand and agree to assume these risks.
YOUR RIGHTS REGARDING THE USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
You have the right at any time to prevent us from contacting you for marketing purposes. When we send a promotional communication to a user, the user can opt out of further promotional communications by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in each promotional e-mail. You can also indicate that you do not wish to receive marketing communications from us in the 'Settings' section of the Site. Please note that notwithstanding the promotional preferences you indicate by either unsubscribing or opting out in the Settings section of the Site, we may continue to send you administrative emails including, for example, periodic updates to our Privacy Policy.
CONTENT
Before downloading or accessing any content, please check if it is potentially 'offensive' or 'adult' content. Deccan Chronicle shall not be responsible for any claims or offense caused or suffered by you accessing such content.
You agree:
To not use the Content available to you on the Site ('Content') for commercial
Not to copy, remove, alter or interfere with any usage
Not to use automated systems or means other than those provided by us for selection or downloading of Content;
Not to give out your password or otherwise allow other people to access the
The Content is owned and controlled by Deccan Chronicle and is protected by intellectual laws.
The third party Content provider is solely responsible for any Content it provides. Deccan Chronicle may be acting as an agent for third party Content provider in providing the Content to you but is not a party to the transaction.
FEEDBACK
When you submit feedback or proposals to Deccan Chronicle through the Service or other means, you acknowledge and agree that DCHL may have similar development ideas to the feedback. You should not give out confidential information about of yourself or any other party. DCHL may freely use, develop and modify feedback for any purpose and that there will be no compensation for such feedback.
ADVERTISEMENTS
Service may include advertisements. Advertisements may be targeted to the content or information stored on the Service, queries made through the Service, or other information.
We would, from time-to-time, pre-fill forms required by advertisers by using data you frequently use on our site. We do this to help you save time from re-entering frequently used information. DCHL will, however, never send any consent information to advertisers or partners of our site without your explicit statement of intent whether it is through having you click a button or otherwise.
COOKIES
Cookies help us to identify your device, or you when you have logged in. We use cookies that are necessary to enable you to navigate the Site. We use cookies to better the website’s functionality by identifying your preferences etc. We also use cookies to help us enhance performance of our Site. We do not sell information collected by our cookies or disclose this information to third parties.
INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY
The Service, Content and Software are protected under the copyright laws. DCHL claims copyrights in its Service, Content, and Software to the maximum extent of the law.
LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES
As part of the Service, we may provide links to other websites or applications. We are not responsible for the privacy practices employed by those websites or the information or content they contain. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by us through the Site and the Service. Therefore, this Privacy Policy does not apply to your use of a third party website accessed by selecting link on our Site or via our Service. To the extent that you access or use the Service through or on another website or application, then the privacy policy of that other website or application will apply to your access or use of that site or application. We encourage our users to read the privacy statements of other websites before proceeding to use them.
CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY
The Company reserves the right to change this policy and our Terms of Service at any time. We will notify you of significant changes to our Privacy Policy by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. Significant changes will go into effect 30 days following such notification. Non-material changes or clarifications will take effect immediately. You should periodically check the Site and this privacy page for updates. Post implementation of such changes, use of the Site and the Service shall be a confirmation of your acceptance of the revised terms. Any and all dispute pertaining to this policy shall be exclusively resolved by the court situated at Hyderabad.
CONTACT US
If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or the practices of this Site, please send an email to online@deccanmail.com.
This Privacy Policy was last updated on 12/02/2016.
Copyright © 2015 - 2020 Deccan Chronicle.
Designed, Developed & Maintained By Daksham
×
Prayers
We have updated our Privacy and Cookie Policy. If you continue to use our site, you agree to the updated Policies.
OK
Also Read:
x
